export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Javascript is an _______ language ?',
        choices: ['Object oriented', 'Object based', 'Procedural','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'Object oriented',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['Var', 'Let', 'A and B', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'A and B',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript ?',
        choices: ['getElementbyId()', 'getElementbyClassName()', 'A and B', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'A and B',
      },
      {
        question: 'Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do ?',
        choices: ['Throws an error', 'Ignores the statements', 'Gives a warning', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Ignores the statements',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript ?',
        choices: ['document.wrie()', 'console.log', 'window.alert()', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },      
      {
        question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type ?',
        choices: ['Const', 'Var', 'Let', 'Constant'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Const',
      },        
      {
        question: 'When the switch statement matches the expression with the given labels, how is the comparison done ?',
        choices: ['Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared', 'Only the datatype of expression is compared','Only the value of expression is compared','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not ?',
        choices: ['In', 'Is in','Exists','Lies'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'In',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['The contents are displayed by non-JS based browsers.', 'Clears all the cookies and cache', 'A and B', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'The contents are displayed by non-JS based browsers',
      },  
      {
        question: 'When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is',
        choices: ['Boolean', 'Undefined', 'Object', 'Integer'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Object',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do ?',
        choices: ['It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime.', 'It acts as a breakpoint in a program.', 'It will debug error in the current statement if any.', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'It acts as a breakpoint in a program.',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What does the ‘toLocateString()’ method do in JS ?',
        choices: ['Returns a localised object representation', 'Returns a parsed string', 'Returns a localized string represetation of an object', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Returns a localized string represetation of an object',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['stringify()', 'parse()', 'convert()', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'stringify()',
      },  
      {
        question: 'The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:',
        choices: ['Class,prototype, object&apos;s parametes', 'Class,prototype, object&apos;s extensible flag', 'Class,parameters, object&apos;s extensible flag','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Class,prototype, object&apos;s extensible flag',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following are closures in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['Variables', 'Functions', 'Objects','All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following is not a Javascript framework ?',
        choices: ['Node', 'React', 'Vue','Cassandra'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Cassandra',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['async', 'await', 'setTimeout', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'async',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How to stop an interval timer in Javascript ?',
        choices: ['clearInterval', 'clearTimer', 'intervalOver','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'clearInterval',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How are objects compared when they are checked with the strict equality operator ?',
        choices: ['The contents of the objects are compared', 'Thier references are compared', 'A and B','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Thier references are compared',
      }, 
      {
        question: 'What does … operator do in JS?',
        choices: ['It is used to spread iterables to individual elements', 'It is used to describe a datatype of undefined size', 'No such operator exists','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'It is used to spread iterables to individual elements',
      }, 
    ],
  };
  